snakkle.com 2019-04-04

# Privacy Policy

**SNAKKLE Privacy Statement**

**(last modified 11/26/2012)**

This Privacy Statement relates to the websites owned or by Snakkle, LLC ( **“SNAKKLE”** ). Additional information regarding your use of the SNAKKLE websites can be found in the Terms of Service located at <https://www.snakkle.com/terms-of-service/>). SNAKKLE may, in its sole discretion, modify or revise this Privacy Statement at any time, and you agree to be bound by such modifications or revisions.

SNAKKLE has created this privacy statement in order to demonstrate its firm commitment to privacy. The following discloses our information gathering and dissemination practices for the SNAKKLE Websites and any other website under which it conducts business.

**1\. A Special Note About Children**

Children under the age of 13 are not eligible to use our services and we ask that such persons not submit personal information to us.Â  We believe that is important that parents supervise their children when they are online.Â  As a result, we require that children under the age of 18 use this service only in conjunction with their parents or guardians.

**2\. Information We Collect and Our Use and Disclosure of Your Information**

> **2.1** We use your IP address to help diagnose problems with our server, and to administer our Web site. Your IP address is also used to gather broad demographic information. ****
> 
> **2.2** We may use cookies on certain pages of our site.Â  Cookies are stored on your hard drive, not on our site.Â  Most cookies are â€œsession cookiesâ€ which means that they are automatically deleted at the end of each session.Â  A cookie itself does not have the ability to automatically collect personal information about you.Â  A cookie can store certain information that identifies your computer to us so that you donâ€™t have to re-enter your password as frequently when you use our site.
> 
> **2.3** Prior to providing us content or signing up to receive email or other notifications, the website may require users to give us contact information including your name, address and phone number and email address, as well as demographic information including zip code (and certain other information that may be optional) ****
> 
> **2\. 4** We also may occasionally send email to our users announcing special promotions changes in our services, and other information we believe will be of interest to our users. Users may opt-out of receiving future mailings; see the choice/opt-out section below.. Demographic and profile data is also collected at our site. This information may be shared with advertisers and our partners on an individual or aggregate basis.
> 
> **2.5** If you send us personal correspondence, such as emails or letters, or if other users or third parties send us correspondence about your activities or postings on our site, we may collect such information into a file specific to you.Â  We use information in the file that we maintain for you, and other information that we obtain from your use of the services, to resolve disputes, troubleshoot problems and enforce our agreement for Terms of Service.
> 
> **2.6** We have partnered with various companies, and gather information regarding preferences which indicate you may be interested in items and products our partners may sell. This information may be made available to those companies on an individual or aggregate basis.
> 
> **2.7** We cannot ensure that all of your private communications and other personally identifiable information will never be disclosed in ways not otherwise described in this Privacy Statement.Â  For example, we may be forced to disclose information to the government or third parties under certain circumstances, or third parties may unlawfully intercept or access transmissions or private communications.Â  We can (and you authorize us to) disclose any information about you to law enforcement or other government officials as we, in our sole discretion, believe necessary or appropriate in connection with an investigation of fraud, intellectual property infringements, or other activity that is illegal or may expose us to legal liability. ****

**3\. Linked Sites**

For your convenience, this site contains links to other sites. SNAKKLE is not responsible for the privacy practices or the content of such Web sites.

**4\. Enforcement**

SNAKKLE regularly reviews its compliance with this Privacy Policy.  When we receive formal written complaints, it is SNAKKLE’S policy to contact the complaining user regarding his or her concerns. We will cooperate with the appropriate regulatory authorities, including local data protection authorities, to resolve any complaints regarding the transfer of personal data that cannot be resolved between SNAKKLE and an individual.

**5\. Security**

This site has security measures in place to protect the loss, misuse and alteration of the information under our control.  All user information stored on our server is stored in an encrypted format. Notwithstanding these efforts, we caution you that “perfect security” does not exist on the Internet.

**6\. Third Party Advertising – Ad Choices**

SNAKKLE’s third-party advertising partners serve ads and collect information when you visit this website. They may also place a cookie on your browser that makes it possible to collect non-personally identifiable information to present more relevant ads on this and other websites. If you would like more information about this practice and to know your choices about not having this information used by these companies, please [click here](http://www.networkadvertising.org/consumer/opt_out.asp).

**7\. Choice/Opt-Out**

This site gives users the following options for removing their information from our database to not receive future communications or to no longer receive our service.  You can send email to newsletter@snakkle.com or you can change your mailing preferences at  [http://_______________](http://_______________/).

**8\. Correct/Update**

This site gives users the following options for changing and modifying information previously provided:  Visit [http://_______________________](http://_______________________/).

**9\. Magnetic**

Snakkle.com allows Magnetic to monitor Snakkle affiliated sites for the purpose of reporting website traffic, statistics, advertisements, “click-throughs” and/or other activities, and such Magnetic may use cookies, web beacons and other monitoring technologies to compile anonymous statistics about Snakkle users.  For further information about Magnetic’s search re-targeting product, Magnetic’s homepage on the Web is located at [http://www.magnetic.is](http://www.magnetic.is/).  The full text of Magnetic’s privacy policy is available on the Web at [http://privacy.magnetic.is](http://privacy.magnetic.is/).  Magnetic may allow third parties to monitor Magnetic associated sites for the purpose of reporting website traffic, statistics, advertisements, “click-throughs” and/or other activities, and such third parties may use cookies, web beacons and other monitoring technologies to compile anonymous statistics about Magnetic users.  Users may go to [http://magnetic.is](http://domdex.com/i) for information on what is being tracked. Users may go to [http://privacy.magnetic.is/w3c/optout.html](http://domdex.com/w3c/optout.html) for information on how to opt-in or opt-out of use of their information by Magnetic and may go to [http://www.networkadvertising.org/managing/opt_out.asp](http://www.networkadvertising.org/managing/opt_out.asp) to opt-out of most third party tracking.

**10\. Contacting SNAKKLE**

If you have any questions about this privacy statement, the practices of this site, or your dealings with this website, you can contact:

SNAKKLE.com  
Email: info@snakkle.com

Fax: 310 882-5443

Fax: 310 882-5443
